<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AntiNarco</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="cardio">
        ☞Cardiovascular diseases (CVDs) are the leading cause of death globally.\n\n
	An estimated 17.9 million people died from CVDs in 2019, representing 32% of all global deaths.
        Of these deaths, 85% were due to heart attack and stroke.\n\n
☞Over three quarters of CVD deaths take place in low- and middle-income countries.\n\n
☞Out of the 17 million premature deaths (under the age of 70) due to noncommunicable diseases in 2019,
        38% were caused by CVDs.\n\n
☞Most cardiovascular diseases can be prevented by addressing behavioural risk factors such as tobacco use,
        unhealthy diet and obesity, physical inactivity and harmful use of alcohol.\n\n
☞It is important to detect cardiovascular disease as early as possible so that management with counselling and medicines can begin.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="stroke">
        ☞A stroke occurs when a blood vessel in the brain ruptures and bleeds, or
        when there s a blockage in the blood supply to the brain.\n\n
        ☞The rupture or blockage prevents blood and oxygen from reaching the brain’s tissues.\n\n
        ☞The loss of blood flow to the brain damages tissues within the brain. \n\n
        ☞Symptoms of a stroke show up in the body parts controlled by the damaged areas of the brain.\n\n
The sooner a person having a stroke gets care, the better their outcome is likely to be.\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="cancer">
   ☞Cancer refers to any one of a large number of diseases characterized by the development of
    abnormal cells that divide uncontrollably and have the ability to infiltrate and destroy normal body tissue.\n\n
    ☞ Cancer often has the ability to spread throughout your body.
    Cancer is the second-leading cause of death in the world.
</string>

    <string name="hivaids">
       ☞Acquired immunodeficiency syndrome AIDS is a chronic, potentially life threatening condition caused by the human
        immunodeficiency virus . By damaging your immune system,\n\n
        ☞HIV interferes with your body s ability to fight infection and disease.
    </string>
    <string name="lung">
        ☞	Lung disease refers to several types of diseases or disorders that prevent the lungs from functioning properly.
        Lung disease can affect respiratory function, or the ability to breathe, and pulmonary function,
        which is how well lungs work.
☞	There are many different lung diseases, some of which are caused by bacterial, viral,
        or fungal infections. Other lung diseases are associated with environmental factors, including asthma,
        mesothelioma, and lung cancer.


    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_dr_yugal">dr_yugal</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
</resources>